Contact

926622723 (Work) gbneves@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gon %C3%A7alo-branco-neves-2b951014 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

AutoCAD Project Management Guitar Player

Languages

English

Gonçalo Branco Neves

CEO na Buildemant - Construção, Manutenção e Soluções Técnicas para Laboratórios, Lda

Lisbon Area, Portugal

Summary

Experienced Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the construction industry. Skilled in AutoCAD, English, Building Maintenance, Microsoft Excel, and Microsoft Word. Strong program and project management professional with a Licenciatura focused in Civil Engineering from Instituto Politécnico de Lisboa.

Experience

Buildemant - Construção e Manutenção, LDA CEO September 2017 - Present

Oeiras, Lisboa, Portugal

Buildemant is a young company founded in 2016 that started developing its activity in the most varied areas related to civil constrution, remodelling and maintenance. After several requests and challenges from our customers and the market itself, we have decided to expand for the area of technical furniture and laboratory equipment.

Positive Field, Lda Gestor de Projecto September 2015 - August 2017 (2 years)

Magnokbilding -Construção Civil Managing Director November 2013 - September 2015 (1 year 11 months)

Energia Cúbica Director da Qualidade January 2012 - October 2013 (1 year 10 months) Rio de Mouro

Parque Escolar Direcção de Contratação May 2010 - December 2011 (1 year 8 months)

Mota-Engil
Departamento Comercial - Orçamento
August 2008 - May 2010 (1 year 10 months)
Planeamento e Orçamento

Anta - Construções Projectos, Lda Fiscalização September 2007 - June 2008 (10 months)

Education

ISEL - Instituto Superior De Engenharia De Lisboa Licenciatura, Civil Engineering · (2004 - 2008)

Escola Machado de Castro Secundário, Curso Tecnológico de Construção Civil · (2000 - 2003)

Salesianos de Lisboa (1994 - 1999)